pubpdf.com 2017-12-14

# PubPDF - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to PubPDF.com is important to us. 

At PubPDF.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit PubPDF.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

In the future, we also may use third party advertisements on PubPDF.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

**National Center for Biotechnology Information Data**

A great deal of scientific data and content on PubPDF.com is retrieved from the National Center for Biotechnology Information's PubMed and MEDLINE databases. In using this site, please comply by [NCBI's Disclaimer and Copyright notice](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/About/disclaimer.html).
